Jonothan Castillo

jonothan.x.castillo@gmail.com, https://github.com/Jonothan98, 832-247-2404, Katy,

Texas 77449

SUMMARY

Adaptable Software Developer with 1-year experience possessing strong communication, problem-solving, and organizational skills. I am seeking a position with a software development company to utilize and enhance my skills to contribute to the production and delivery of software products meeting client specifications and requirements.

SKILLS / SOFTWARE

• React, Spring boot, Node Js, C++, C#, Java, Javascript, TypeScript, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bitbucket, Git, Automated Testing, Selenium, Microservices, Unity, Object Oriented Programming, MySQL, Agile, Test Driven Development, Continues Integration/Continuous Deployment

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Digital Media with a Minor in Computer Science

- University of Houston- Main Campus, Houston, Texas
- Graduated: December 17, 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS Practitioner Certified
- Certified SAFe Practitioner

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer (Remote)

TEKsystems

Katy, Texas -2022 to 2023

- Developed efficient and elegant code in accordance with project requirements
- Used SAFe Scaled Agile development methodologies to deliver value quickly and frequently, such as test-driven development and SAFe Scrum
- Pursued continuous professional development, obtaining AWS Practitioner and SAFe Practitioner Certification
- Designed and executed integration and unit tests for a React-based e-commerce site using Selenium
- Employed version control tools like Bitbucket and Git for efficient source code management

Cashier

Hobby Lobby

Houston, Texas -2021 to 2022

- Cashier, checking out customer purchases
- Assisted customers with any product inquiries
- · Stocking and organizing merchandise

Customer Service

Office of Registrar in the University of Houston Welcome Center Houston, Texas – 2016 to 2021

- Organized files and documents
- · Assisted students who had questions specific to our department
- Guided students in the submission and request of transcripts, VA benefits, verification of enrollments, and residency reclassifications
- Collaborated in converting all hard copy files into digital format

Sales Clerk

S and B Fireworks

Katy, Texas -2012 to 2020

- Stock and maintain inventory of fireworks on display
- Assist customers in the selection of their desired type of fireworks
- Assist in the selling transactions using the cash register
- Box up and store fireworks in a storage unit at the end of the firework season.

Sales Clerk

Bill's Blazin' BBQ/Wood Lot

Katy, Texas -2012 to 2016

- Split and organize wood by type, length, and client preference to be sold.
- Assist customers in finding their desired type of wood, such as for barbequing or fireplaces.
- Sell and load the wood for the customer.